각각의 gate에 대한 gating values은
The gating values for each gate get
입력 파라메터에 대한 간단한 로직스틱회귀에
의해서 조절되어집니다.
controlled by a tiny logistic
regression on the input parameters.
각각의 gate는 파라메터를 공유합니다.
Each of them has its own
set of shared parameters.
추가되어 있는 hyperbolic tension은
And there's an additional hyperbolic
tension sprinkled in here
-1 과 1사이의 출력을 유지하기 위해서입니다.
to keep the outputs between -1 and 1.
이것은 복잡해보이지만 수학으로 쓸수 있습니다.
It looks complicated but
once you write down the math
할당문에서 보는것 같이
이것은 말 그대로 다섯줄의 코드입니다.
It's literally five lines of code,
as you'll see in the assignment.
이것은 잘 동작하고 연속이며 모든 방법으로 미분 가능하며,
And it's well-behaved, continues,
and differentiable all the way,
매우 쉽게 이것의 파라메터를을
최적화 할 수 있다는 의미입니다.
which means we can optimize
those parameters very easily.
그래서 왜 LSTM은 동작합니까?
So why do LSTMs work?
너무 많은 상세사항 없이도,
모든 gate들은 모델에 도움이 됩니다.
Without going into too many details,
all these little gates help the model
필요할때는 메모리를 더 오래 유지하고
필요없을때는 그것을 무시하도록 해서
keep its memory longer when it needs to,
and ignore things when it should.
결과로써, 최적화는 더 쉽고
As a result,
the optimization is much easier, and
gradient vanishing는 사라집니다.
the gradient vanishing, vanishes.